[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Are you primed and ready for the kill?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "primed", "and", "ready", "for", "the", "kill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "I am feeling good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "feeling", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Is that what it feels like?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "it", "feels", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How many times have you relived that 0.17 of a second?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "times", "have", "you", "relived", "that", "0.17", "of", "a", "second", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I feel like every day since then.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "like", "every", "day", "since", "then", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What are you not allowed to do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "not", "allowed", "to", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "Well, you know, you have to cut down on all your social activities.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "have", "to", "cut", "down", "on", "all", "your", "social", "activities", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Are you allowed even in your height of training, are you allowed to have binge eating days?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "allowed", "even", "in", "your", "height", "of", "training", ",", "are", "you", "allowed", "to", "have", "binge", "eating", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "Yes, you are.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "And is it true there's like this group wide sex ban on the entire American team before the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["And", "is", "it", "true", "there", "'s", "like", "this", "group", "wide", "sex", "ban", "on", "the", "entire", "American", "team", "before", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I didn't -- I didn't know about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "n't", "--", "I", "did", "n't", "know", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Is it what?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Literally, none of you are allowed to do anything like that.", "answer_tokens": ["Literally", ",", "none", "of", "you", "are", "allowed", "to", "do", "anything", "like", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "What are you thinking of?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "thinking", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "Well, I'm praying for God.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "praying", "for", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "How are you going to be feeling?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "going", "to", "be", "feeling", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "Mixed emotions.", "answer_tokens": ["Mixed", "emotions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Because when you're on the podium, and you won the gold for the relay, are you still thinking this is great, but it's not the same?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "when", "you", "'re", "on", "the", "podium", ",", "and", "you", "won", "the", "gold", "for", "the", "relay", ",", "are", "you", "still", "thinking", "this", "is", "great", ",", "but", "it", "'s", "not", "the", "same", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "ELIX: It's not the same.", "answer_tokens": ["ELIX", ":", "It", "'s", "not", "the", "same", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "Personally and professionally?", "question_tokens": ["Personally", "and", "professionally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "Well, personally, my family.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "personally", ",", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Isn't she the one with the phenomenal nails?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "she", "the", "one", "with", "the", "phenomenal", "nails", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "She has nails in her family.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "has", "nails", "in", "her", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "Aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Thank you.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "You think about the commercial benefit to winning the gold?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "about", "the", "commercial", "benefit", "to", "winning", "the", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "Well, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "ORGAN: Got a man in your life?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Got", "a", "man", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "I do, I have a man.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", ",", "I", "have", "a", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "What does he do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "He's done a little running in his time but he's kind of transitioning out of it and just getting ready for the next phase of his life.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "done", "a", "little", "running", "in", "his", "time", "but", "he", "'s", "kind", "of", "transitioning", "out", "of", "it", "and", "just", "getting", "ready", "for", "the", "next", "phase", "of", "his", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Wedding bells?", "question_tokens": ["Wedding", "bells", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "My mind doesn't function so after the --", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mind", "does", "n't", "function", "so", "after", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 212, "question": "Are you allowed to even be thinking about this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "allowed", "to", "even", "be", "thinking", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 213, "answer": "I can't even -- I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "even", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "Are you more or less likely to marry him if you win gold?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "more", "or", "less", "likely", "to", "marry", "him", "if", "you", "win", "gold", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Well, I'm going to be in such a good mood.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "be", "in", "such", "a", "good", "mood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "You would do anything, wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "do", "anything", ",", "would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "Probably would.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "When you think of her story what do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "think", "of", "her", "story", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "It's disappointing, especially for me because when I got into traffic and field, she was everywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "disappointing", ",", "especially", "for", "me", "because", "when", "I", "got", "into", "traffic", "and", "field", ",", "she", "was", "everywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for her?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "sympathy", "for", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "It's very hard for me to have sympathy, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "hard", "for", "me", "to", "have", "sympathy", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Do you have suspicions about some of your rivals?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "suspicions", "about", "some", "of", "your", "rivals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "ELIX: Well, of course.", "answer_tokens": ["ELIX", ":", "Well", ",", "of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Like your body changing.", "answer_tokens": ["Like", "your", "body", "changing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "When you line up for the 200-meter final, how many people in that race could be cheats?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "line", "up", "for", "the", "200-meter", "final", ",", "how", "many", "people", "in", "that", "race", "could", "be", "cheats", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Wow, that's a tough question.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "tough", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "make", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "It's hard.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "How does that work with a dog?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "work", "with", "a", "dog", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "She's very smart, but I mean -- I will tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "very", "smart", ",", "but", "I", "mean", "--", "I", "will", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 320, "question": "It's going to be a huge moment for you, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "huge", "moment", "for", "you", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 321, "answer": "It is, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How do you feel about being an American flying the flag for America at such a prestigious event?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "an", "American", "flying", "the", "flag", "for", "America", "at", "such", "a", "prestigious", "event", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "So proud.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "proud", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Maybe it's time to stand up, beat your chest and show the Chinese who's real boss?", "question_tokens": ["Maybe", "it", "'s", "time", "to", "stand", "up", ",", "beat", "your", "chest", "and", "show", "the", "Chinese", "who", "'s", "real", "boss", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "If you win, what's the plan after that once you've achieved your great aim?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "win", ",", "what", "'s", "the", "plan", "after", "that", "once", "you", "'ve", "achieved", "your", "great", "aim", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Oh, my gosh, I have no plan.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "gosh", ",", "I", "have", "no", "plan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marion"]}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Is that the way to really tackle this?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "way", "to", "really", "tackle", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I think it's tough because situations like Marion, you know, she never failed a drug test.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "tough", "because", "situations", "like", "Marion", ",", "you", "know", ",", "she", "never", "failed", "a", "drug", "test", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "That would -- that would root it out, wouldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "would", "--", "that", "would", "root", "it", "out", ",", "would", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RP", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Well, you'd have to be a very rich man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "'d", "have", "to", "be", "a", "very", "rich", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "I mean do you have to have that streak of self-confidence?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "do", "you", "have", "to", "have", "that", "streak", "of", "self-confidence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "I think it's part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Which one are you going to take?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "one", "are", "you", "going", "to", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "CD", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I'm taking the gold.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "taking", "the", "gold", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "Is that true?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "I guess, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "guess", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "Is that how you see yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "how", "you", "see", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "I see myself as a normal 19-year-old kid.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "see", "myself", "as", "a", "normal", "19-year-old", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "Who just happens to be a gold medal contending power ball?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "just", "happens", "to", "be", "a", "gold", "medal", "contending", "power", "ball", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "Yes, I guess.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "guess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "What was it like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Growing up in the Bronx, especially as a gymnast, not easy.", "answer_tokens": ["Growing", "up", "in", "the", "Bronx", ",", "especially", "as", "a", "gymnast", ",", "not", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "It wasn't masculine enough for them?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "n't", "masculine", "enough", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 465, "question": "Why gymnastics?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "gymnastics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 466, "answer": "I love -- I took gymnastics because it's one of the most challenging sports in the world and that's what I love about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "--", "I", "took", "gymnastics", "because", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "most", "challenging", "sports", "in", "the", "world", "and", "that", "'s", "what", "I", "love", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 512, "question": "What are the good parts of you that you think come from being a Bronx guy?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "good", "parts", "of", "you", "that", "you", "think", "come", "from", "being", "a", "Bronx", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 513, "answer": "I mean, well, look at my parents.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "well", ",", "look", "at", "my", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Did you get into fights as a kid in the Bronx?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "into", "fights", "as", "a", "kid", "in", "the", "Bronx", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "I --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "Did everybody have to fight if you're a young man growing up in the Bronx?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "everybody", "have", "to", "fight", "if", "you", "'re", "a", "young", "man", "growing", "up", "in", "the", "Bronx", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Knives as well?", "question_tokens": ["Knives", "as", "well", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Was he stabbed?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "stabbed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "No, thanks god.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "thanks", "god", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What did it teach you, the incident?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "it", "teach", "you", ",", "the", "incident", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "That life is unpredictable and you can't let -- you can't hold on to that.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "life", "is", "unpredictable", "and", "you", "ca", "n't", "let", "--", "you", "ca", "n't", "hold", "on", "to", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "What does it take to be as good as you are at what you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "take", "to", "be", "as", "good", "as", "you", "are", "at", "what", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "I would say it takes a lot of willpower and a lot of sacrifice and a lot of self-motivation.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "say", "it", "takes", "a", "lot", "of", "willpower", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "sacrifice", "and", "a", "lot", "of", "self-motivation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 590, "question": "What are you, 19?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", ",", "19", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 591, "answer": "Nineteen.", "answer_tokens": ["Nineteen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "This is not a world that you're allowed to do, right?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "not", "a", "world", "that", "you", "'re", "allowed", "to", "do", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "It's not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "JJS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "If you perform at your absolute best, what can you achieve in London?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "perform", "at", "your", "absolute", "best", ",", "what", "can", "you", "achieve", "in", "London", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJS", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I think if I do my absolute best, I think I might have a chance at being on the medal stand, top three in all-around.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "if", "I", "do", "my", "absolute", "best", ",", "I", "think", "I", "might", "have", "a", "chance", "at", "being", "on", "the", "medal", "stand", ",", "top", "three", "in", "all-around", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "If you win a gold, how is that going to make you feel, a boy from the Bronx winning an Olympic gold medal, standing on that podium, the American National Anthem playing?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "win", "a", "gold", ",", "how", "is", "that", "going", "to", "make", "you", "feel", ",", "a", "boy", "from", "the", "Bronx", "winning", "an", "Olympic", "gold", "medal", ",", "standing", "on", "that", "podium", ",", "the", "American", "National", "Anthem", "playing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "That would be a dream come true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "would", "be", "a", "dream", "come", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["American National Anthem"], "LOCATION": ["Bronx"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "It would be an emotional moment for you, huh?", "question_tokens": ["It", "would", "be", "an", "emotional", "moment", "for", "you", ",", "huh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Definitely an emotional moment for me and my family.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "an", "emotional", "moment", "for", "me", "and", "my", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "Really, I am?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "I", "am", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "That's what I'm hearing.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "I", "'m", "hearing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Are you ready for screaming women chasing you down the street?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "ready", "for", "screaming", "women", "chasing", "you", "down", "the", "street", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 630, "question": "-- shoot up in your face as you stand there?", "question_tokens": ["--", "shoot", "up", "in", "your", "face", "as", "you", "stand", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 631, "answer": "No, never.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "never", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "A tiny little bit of told you?", "question_tokens": ["A", "tiny", "little", "bit", "of", "told", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 634, "question": "Come on, it will be a little bit, won't it?", "question_tokens": ["Come", "on", ",", "it", "will", "be", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "wo", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 635, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "I don't mean vengeful, but more like vindication?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "mean", "vengeful", ",", "but", "more", "like", "vindication", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "Maybe a little bit.", "answer_tokens": ["Maybe", "a", "little", "bit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "Being an American?", "question_tokens": ["Being", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "It's like, whoa, Coach K. Why are you such a big deal?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "like", ",", "whoa", ",", "Coach", "K.", "Why", "are", "you", "such", "a", "big", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "Well, you must have a lot of Polish people on your staff.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "must", "have", "a", "lot", "of", "Polish", "people", "on", "your", "staff", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 672, "question": "What does it mean to you to have that reputation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "to", "you", "to", "have", "that", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 673, "answer": "Well, I've been lucky to be at place where their brand helped me right away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "been", "lucky", "to", "be", "at", "place", "where", "their", "brand", "helped", "me", "right", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "And what are you going to do to stop it from happening in London, when the whole world assumes you're going to win gold quite easily?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "are", "you", "going", "to", "do", "to", "stop", "it", "from", "happening", "in", "London", ",", "when", "the", "whole", "world", "assumes", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "win", "gold", "quite", "easily", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Well, the very first thing is you don't go with assumptions.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "very", "first", "thing", "is", "you", "do", "n't", "go", "with", "assumptions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["London"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 719, "question": "How do you get it to gel and to work, where they have to share that status?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "get", "it", "to", "gel", "and", "to", "work", ",", "where", "they", "have", "to", "share", "that", "status", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 720, "answer": "Well, the very first thing is you're honest with them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "very", "first", "thing", "is", "you", "'re", "honest", "with", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "Is the American dream still as attainable as it was when you were young?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "American", "dream", "still", "as", "attainable", "as", "it", "was", "when", "you", "were", "young", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "You know, I don't think it is.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 746, "question": "But if they are driven out of an education system that doesn't nurture them, then how can we blame them?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "they", "are", "driven", "out", "of", "an", "education", "system", "that", "does", "n't", "nurture", "them", ",", "then", "how", "can", "we", "blame", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 747, "answer": "Intellect does not know race, color, nationality, gender.", "answer_tokens": ["Intellect", "does", "not", "know", "race", ",", "color", ",", "nationality", ",", "gender", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", "IN", "CD", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 755, "question": "What are the values you like to instill in them, human values?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "values", "you", "like", "to", "instill", "in", "them", ",", "human", "values", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 756, "answer": "The main thing is to be truthful, where you're honest with one another.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "main", "thing", "is", "to", "be", "truthful", ",", "where", "you", "'re", "honest", "with", "one", "another", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 765, "question": "What does it take to be a champion sportsman, not just a winner or a good sportsman, or even necessarily a great sportsman, but a champion over a long period of time?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "take", "to", "be", "a", "champion", "sportsman", ",", "not", "just", "a", "winner", "or", "a", "good", "sportsman", ",", "or", "even", "necessarily", "a", "great", "sportsman", ",", "but", "a", "champion", "over", "a", "long", "period", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 766, "answer": "Well, incredible commitment.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "incredible", "commitment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kobe Bryant", "Lebron James", "Chris Paul"], "LOCATION": ["London"]}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 775, "question": "The first game?", "question_tokens": ["The", "first", "game", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 776, "answer": "In London, looking around Kobe Bryant, Lebron James, Chris Paul, whoever you choose as your starters.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "London", ",", "looking", "around", "Kobe", "Bryant", ",", "Lebron", "James", ",", "Chris", "Paul", ",", "whoever", "you", "choose", "as", "your", "starters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 777, "question": "What do you say to guys like that in that moment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "guys", "like", "that", "in", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 778, "answer": "You keep it simple.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "keep", "it", "simple", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "When you see somebody like him, as a sportsman yourself, is the resounding lesson to just know when to stop?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "see", "somebody", "like", "him", ",", "as", "a", "sportsman", "yourself", ",", "is", "the", "resounding", "lesson", "to", "just", "know", "when", "to", "stop", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "I think we don't know when to stop.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "when", "to", "stop", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120704pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 816, "question": "If you get badly beaten by a young whipper snapper, how are you going to feel?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "get", "badly", "beaten", "by", "a", "young", "whipper", "snapper", ",", "how", "are", "you", "going", "to", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 817, "answer": "I'm going to feel OK.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "feel", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]